themify.me 2019-06-25

# Privacy Policy • Themify

Themify values your privacy and protecting your information is critically important to us. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

### What personal information do we collect from you when visiting our website?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address or other details to help you with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, use Live Chat, open a Support Ticket, provide us with feedback on our products or services, or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you in the following ways:

  * To allow us to better serve you in customer service responses and to improve our website.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To ask for reviews of services or products.
  * To follow up with you after correspondence (email, forum, live chat, or phone).

### How do we protect your information?

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order, and enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

### PayPal

When you use PayPal to pay for your order, you will provide your personal information and credit card number, directly to PayPal. The information you provide on the PayPal website will be protected by PayPal’s privacy policy.

### Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  * Help remember a user’s login session.
  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browsers are all a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

### Third-Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third-Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or requests or questions.
  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.Send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has   occurred.  

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

****If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from future emails, you can:****

  * Email us at: info@themify.me  

  * Or click ‘ **Unsubscribe** ’ at the bottom of each email.

**If at any time you would like to review and delete your account information, you can:**

  * Email us at: info@themify.me

### Privacy Policy Changes

Themify may change its Privacy Policy from time to time. Most changes are likely to be minor and at Themify’s sole discretion. Themify encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

**Email:**[info@themify.me](mailto:info@themify.me)

**Address:**  
Themify  
55 Adelaide St E  
Toronto, ON M5C 1K6   
Canada

Last edited on 2018-05-18
